Size all the up down boxes

Finish the wheeling interface and implement
I am currently using a MessageBox (in five places)which does not honor the user’s theme colors – is a custom panel. Adopt for CurlyPad as well.

new coding tool:
So, while the broader term is "expression-bodied member," specifically for a method, it's called an expression-bodied method. This syntax is useful for making concise and readable code when the method's logic consists of a single expression. 
// Traditional method definition
void Method() {
    AnotherMethod();
}

// Expression-bodied method definition
void Method() => AnotherMethod();

dirty exit - reimage & doc
scroller buttons in the toolbar w/ keyboard (alt) shortcuts - ¿reimage & doc?

new menu items:
	wheeling and its subitems
	copy to beginning
	copy to end
	trim to beginning
	trim to end
		document & reimage

Edges, scroll & page [up down right left], buttons in toolbar & “alt” messages
	document

Unhandled exception on search – ¿moon phase?


I will try to keep track of “what is new ‘today’”:
a couple of bugs related to dynamically picking/changing Themes
Find/Search/Replace text boxes all automatically select all when you focus them

Notes:
The current line percentage is not accurate when wordwrap is turned on.
Neither the font picker (which gives access to the two font’s foreground/pen color)
nor the color picker (both backgrounds) are very Dragon-friendly.
